A Flintstone Christmas is a animation, tv movie, comedy
film directed by Charles August Nichols.
Santa has an accident at Fred's house on Christmas Eve, Fred
and Barney have to continue his run for him.
Fred Flintstone (voice), played by Henry Corden.
Barney Rubble / Dino (voice), played by Mel Blanc.
Wilma Flintstone / Pebbles Flintstone (voice), played by Jean Vander Pyl.
Betty Rubble (voice), played by Gay Autterson.
Bamm Bamm Rubble (voice), played by Lucille Bliss.
Mr. George Nate Slate (voice), played by John Stephenson.
A Flintstone Christmas is a 1977 animated Christmas television special
featuring characters from The Flintstones franchise.
It was produced by Hanna-Barbera and is the second Christmas-themed animated work in the franchise, after the 1964
episode "Christmas Flintstone." Both feature the character Fred Flintstone taking on the role of Santa Claus.
The special first aired on NBC on December 7, 1977.
The special has been released on VHS and DVD.
It is followed by two more Flintstones Christmas specials, A Flintstone
Family Christmas (1993) and A Flintstones Christmas Carol (1994).
The film explores themes of holiday, santa claus, family
relationships, alternate history, anachronism.
The tone is lighthearted.